Guy Louden is an Australian artist and curator living in Fremantle/ Wayalup and born in Toronto. He has managed and founded experimental galleries and curated major exhibitions. His artwork has been exhibited in Sydney, Melbourne, Perth, regionally and online.

Louden holds an MA in Art History from the University of Manchester (2013), a Master of Art Curating from the University of Sydney (2018), and a BA from the University of Western Australia (2011).

Contact: guypatricklouden@gmail.com

Education

2018 Master of Art Curating, University of Sydney
2012-13 Master of Arts (Art History),
University of Manchester
2008-11 Bachelor of Arts (Fine Arts,
English), University of Western Australia
2009-10 Study abroad scholarship
University of California, Los Angeles

Exhibitions (selected)

- Co-curator and Artist, *Preppers*, Fremantle Arts Centre, 2019
- Artist, Spring1883, Sydney, 2019
- Artist, *Network Archeology*, Cool Change Contemporary, 2019
- Artist, WROL, Bus Projects, 2018
- Artist and Co-curator, SHTF, Firstdraft, 2017
- Artist, *Preppers*, Polizia, 2017
- Curator and Artist, *GaiaGolf*, Claremont

Arts Festival 2017

- Artist, *Outdoor Kit*, ArtTra festival, 2017
- Curator and Artist, Bye, Success, 2016
- Curator, No Confidence, Perth International Arts Festival, 2016
- Curator, *Theatres*, Perth International Arts Festival, 2015
- Curator, *Specific Gravity*, Moana Project Space, 2015

Publications (selected)

- Essay, *Frictionless*: Dan McCabe, Outer Space ARI, 2019
- Catalogue Text, Memories of the Network Age: Network Archeology, Cool Change, 2019
- Exhibition Exegesis, No Confidence: PIAF Visual Arts Guide, 2016
- Catalogue Essay, *Khazi*: Lilly Kaiser, Moana Project Space, 2015
- Exhibition Exegesis, *Theatres*: Perth International Arts Festival Guide, 2015
- Essay, *Hyperborea*, Free Range, 2014
- Catalogue Essay, Warning: Simon Finn, Moana Project Space, 2013

Residencies

- Fremantle Arts Centre, 2017
- Curatorial Exchange, hosted by Artspace, 2016

Professional Experience

- Assistant Gallery Curator, Heathcote Cultural Precinct, 2019-
- Senior Technician, Carriageworks,

2018-2019

- Art Install Technician, Fremantle Arts Centre, 2017
- Artist Field Officer/GA, Warakurna Artists, 2017
- Founder/Member, Polizia studio gallery, Fremantle 2017
- Art Install Technician, Wesfarmers Collection, 2016, 2019
- Artist Field Officer/GA, Martumili Arts, 2016
- Founder/Program Manager, Success, 2015
- Director, Moana Project Space, 2014-2017